Guide to the Myron Gustin Fincher Papers, 1908-1993
Fincher, Myron Gustin papers, 1908-1993
- Series VIII. Cornell Office Files
  - 1960-1961
    - Annual Report, 1960-1961 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Annual Report, 1959-1961 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - A.V.M.A., 1960-1961 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - A.V.M.A., 1960-1961 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - A.V.M.A.-Prospectus Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - A.V.M.A.-Executive Board, 1960-1961 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - A.V.M.A.-Providence Meeting, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - ADSA-AVMA, 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Annual Vet. Conference, 1960-1962 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - A.R.S.-Dale Suplee, 1960-1961 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - B, 1960-1961 (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Baler, J.A., 1959 (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - Veterinary College Herd-Mastitis, 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Beacon Milling Co., 1961 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Brazil, 1959-1961 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Medical Department Annual Report, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - C, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Circular Letters-Departmental, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Clinical Pathological Conference, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - D, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Drug Price List, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Dwarfism, ca. 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Gov.Thomas E. Dewey, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - E, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Employer-Employee, 1959-1961 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - F, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Fairs- Health Certificates, etc., 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - F.D.A., ca. 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Foreign Visitors, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Farm and Home Week, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - F.H. Fox, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - G, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - GLF Mastitis-Feed Experiment, 1959-1961 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Dr. R.S. Guthrie, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Graduate School, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Tripathy, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Kazuya, Usui, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - H, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Hanover Shoe Farms, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - H.G. Hodges, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Horse Practice, Short Course, Jan. 1961 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - I, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Requests for Information-Laymen, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Requests for Information-Veterinarians, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - J, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - K, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - F.V. Kosikowski, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Budget Requests, 1961-1962 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Budget Requests, 1961-1962 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Budget Requests, 1962-1963 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - L.C. Kent-Letters, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - L, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Library, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - M, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Milk Sales (Vet. College to Dairy Industry), Mar. 29, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Dave Morrow, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - McDonald Farms, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - McDonald Farms, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - Jolly Val., 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 49)
    - Machold Farms, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 50)
    - Mastitis, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 51)
    - 1956 Expansion-Mastitis Program, 1956-1959 (Box 28, Folder 52)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Amsterdam, NY, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 53)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Canton, NY, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 54)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Earlville, NY, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 55)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Kingston, NY, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 56)
    - Mastitis Control Program-East Aurora, NY (Box 28, Folder 57)
    - Meetings Attended, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Merck, Sharp and Dohme Co., 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - G.E. Morse, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - N, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - N.YC. Milk Area Physical Examinations-Revised Sanitary Code, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - N.Y.S. Veterinary Medical Society, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Norden Labs, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - O, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - P, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Dean Poppensick, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - 1960-61 Annual Report Data, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Pennsylvania Veterinary Supply Co., 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Parentage Proof, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Pfizer and Col, Chas., 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Pitman-Moore Co., 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Purchasing Dept., 1960 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - R, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Retirement Set-up, 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Reprints Sent, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Ripley Laboratory, 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - S.J. Roberts, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - S, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - South American Trip, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - State Institution Farms, G.R. Gilbert, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Sterling-Winthrop-Bovine Immune Globulin Exp., 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Smith, Kline & French, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - E.R. Squibb and Sons, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Sterility (Vibriosis), ca. 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Student Information, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Student Dormitory and Student Help, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - T, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Tice, A.K.-Cortland, N.Y., 1961 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - U, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Upjohn-Ulbamycin, pen, etc., 1960 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - V, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Veterinarians Wanted, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - W, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - XYZ, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - 1961-1962
    - A, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - Ankony Farms, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 40)
    - Agricultural Progress Day, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - American Breeder's Service, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - American Council on Education, 1960-1962 (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - Staph. Aureus Toxiod Exp. And American Cynamid- Main,Warran and Coye Farms, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - A.V.M.A. Executive Board, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 45)
    - A.V.M.A. Meeting in Miami, Florida (1), 1961 (Box 29, Folder 46)
    - A.V.M.A. Meeting in Miami, Florida (2), 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 47)
    - A.V.M.A., 1960-1962 (Box 29, Folder 48)
    - A.V.M.A. Prospectus Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 49)
    - H.E. Kingman-Executive Secretary of the A.V.M.A., 1962 (Box 29, Folder 50)
    - A.V.M.A. Council on Education, ca. 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 51)
    - A.V.M.A.-D.A. Price, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 52)
    - A.D.S.-A.V.M.A. Joint Meeting, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 53)
    - B, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 54)
    - College Veterinary Barns, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 55)
    - Beef, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 56)
    - Bureau of Animal Industry-G.S. Kaley, 1960-1962 (Box 29, Folder 57)
    - C, 1960-1962 (Box 29, Folder 58)
    - Catalase Test, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 59)
    - Cattle Disease Review, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 60)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 29, Folder 61)
    - Clinical Pathology Conference, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 62)
    - D, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 63)
    - Danks-Lease Renewal, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 64)
    - Gov.Thomas E. Dewey, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 65)
    - Drug and Chemical Companies, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 66)
    - E, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 67)
    - F, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 68)
    - Furst-Pearlstone (Gumaer), 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - G, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Grange League Federation (G.L.F.), 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Graduate School, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - H, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Hanover Shoe Farm, 1959-1962 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Hamilton, Bertha L., Trust, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Honor Day Exercises, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Hodges, H.G., 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - I, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Infectious Diseases Meeting, June 18-22, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Information Requests for Veterinarians, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - International Fertility Association, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - J, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - K, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - L, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - M, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Machold Farm, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Mastitis-R Barn Experiment, 1960-1962 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Mastitis-Nemco, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Project "M" (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Mastitis-Central Office Income, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Amsterdam, NY, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Canton, NY, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Earlville, NY, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Kingston, NY, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Mastitis Control Program-East Aurora, NY, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - "Field Experiences with the NYS Mastitis Program", 1961 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - McDonald Farms, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - McDonald Farms, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Meetings Attended, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous Inquiries, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Mobile Veterinary Dispensary, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - N, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - N.Y.S. Government Departments, 1959-1962 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - N.Y.S. Veterinary Medical Society, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - O, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - P, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Pan American Veterinary Conference, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - Pan American Veterinary Conference, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Pan American Veterinary Conference, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - Programs, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Purchasing Department Meeting, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - R, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - S, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - Student Dorm, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - T, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 47)
    - Talks, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 48)
    - U, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 49)
    - University Policy Committee, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 50)
    - Uruguay, Universidade de la, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 51)
    - U.S.D.A., 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 52)
    - V, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 53)
    - A.C. Income and Night Calls, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 54)
    - Annual Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 55)
    - Annual Veterinary Conference, Jan. 10-12, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 56)
    - L.C. Kent Letters, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 57)
    - L.C. Kent Finances, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 58)
    - Dean's Office, 1958-1962 (Box 30, Folder 59)
    - Inter-Office Communication, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 60)
    - Library, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 61)
    - Surgery Department, 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Veterinarians Wanted, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Virus Research Institute, 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - W, 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - 1962-1963
    - A, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Alfred Agricultural and Technical Institute, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Coye Herd, 1961-1963 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - General Cochrane Herd, 1961-1963 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - American Breeder's Service, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - A.V.M.A., 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - A.V.M.A., 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - A.V.M.A., 1963 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - A.V.M.A.-Insurance Trust Problem (Dr. Sheford S. Miller), 1963 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - A.V.M.A.-meetings, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - A.V.M.A.-meetings, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - A.V.M.A.-Annual Meeting, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - A.V.M.A. - New York City, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - A.V.M.A. - T.V. Presentations, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - A.V.M.A. New York City Meeting-Prospectus Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - A.V.M.A.- Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - A.V.M.A.- Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - A.V.M.A.-Robert Getty, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - A.V.M.A.-H.G. Hodges, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - A.V.M.A.-H.E. Kingman, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - A.V.M.A.-Donald A. Price, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - A.V.M.A.-John Bullard, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - A.V.M.A.-D.F. Walker, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - A.V.M.A.-Prospectus Committee, 1961-1963 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Animal Husbandry Herds, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - U.S.D.A.-Agricultural Research Service, 1961-1963 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - B, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Dr. Jack Beattie-White Gates Farm, Mr. Eugene Denton, Owner; Mr. Robert Connell, manager, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - "R" Barn, 1962-1963 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - C, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Dank's Lease Renewal, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - D-E, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Drug and Chemical Companies, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Dewey, Thomas E., 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Haver-Lockhart Laboratories, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - Mead-Johnson, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Ray Chemical, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - Schering Corporation, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - Upjohn Co., 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - F, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 46)
    - Gibbons - Cattle Diseases Revision, 1960-1961 (Box 31, Folder 47)
    - G, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 48)
    - K.I. Gumaer, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 49)
    - Grange League Federation-DeCamp, Beals, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - H, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - International Congress on Animal Reproduction and Artificial Insemination, Sept. 6-13, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - International Fertility Association, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Medical Services Advisory Committee, Sept. 1, 1962-Sept. 1, 1965, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Mastitis Control Program, 1961-1963 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Mastitis - Strep A. Elimination Plan, Nov. 10, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Metzger-National Mastitis Council Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Project "M", 1962 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Mastitis Control Program, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - McDonald Farms, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Inquiries, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Department of Agriculture and Markets, Commissioner, Wickham, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - N.Y.S. Veterinary Medical Society, 1961-1963 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - O-P, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Ketosis Project-Grange League Federation, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - State Institution Farms-G.R. Gilbert, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Still House Hollow Farm, Middleburg, Va., Dr. R.L. Booth, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - T-U, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - U.S.D.A., 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - V, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Annual Report, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Entertainment of Non-Resident Lecturers-Annual Veterinary Conference, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Poppensiek, George, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Danks, A. G., 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Veterinary Virus Research Institute, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Requests for Veterinarians, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - W, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 29)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
A number of article reprints have been removed from the collection. A list of them is available in Series VII.Veterinary Ephemera. Many of the original reprints are available in the Veterinary Reprint and Pamphlet Collection, #24-04-3369.